Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/ar-shamika-shirke-15203088 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Public Speaking Microsoft Office AutoCAD

Languages

English (Full Professional) Hindi (Full Professional) Marathi (Full Professional)

Certifications

Licensed Architect environmental design solutions

Publications

2D composition to 3D

Ar. Shamika Shirke

Architect

Mumbai, Maharashtra, India

Summary

Experienced Architect with a demonstrated history of working in the architecture & planning along with construction industry. Skilled in AutoCAD, Windows 10, Microsoft Word, Computer-Aided Design (CAD), and Creative Concept Design. Strong arts and design professional post graduated from Maharashtra Institute of Technology.

Experience

S.B.Architects Architect September 2016 - Present Mumbai

The major work duties include, Preparation of preliminary/ architectural designs & Municipal drawings and visiting the site, to check the work carried out as per approved plans. Majorly working with " SUMER GROUP OF COMPANIES, AR.HAFEEZ CONTRACTOR, TALATHY & PANTHAKY ARCHITECTS"

environmental design solutions Trainee February 2014 - 2014 (less than a year) Mumbai

This training was meant for practicing Architects, students, Engineers which was emphasized on "Passive Solar Design, Daylight & Simulations For Green Buildings".

Software designed by EDS has helped architects, engineers, building owners, and operators in designing and operating more sustainable buildings. EDS has designed analytical tools which are used extensively by reputed institutions worldwide for policy analysis, building thermal comfort and energy end use analysis. They have also designed interactive software to inform occupants about the impact of their behavior and lifestyle choices on the sustainability of their workplaces and homes which was a part of this training.

This program was conducted by the EDS Pvt. Ltd. (Environmental Design Solutions) and was supported by the Ministry of New and Renewable Energy, Government Of India and IIHS (Indian Institute For Human Settlements).

Vikrant Karia institute of arts Executive Administrative Head August 2012 - December 2012 (5 months) Mumbai Area, India

Working with proper data entries, compiling various portfolios of creative ranking students with their works.

Education

Maharashtra Institute of Technology

Post Graduation in Construction Project Management, Project

Management (2017 - 2018)

Rizvi college of architecture, Bandra. B.arch, Architecture · (2012 - 2017)

EDS Pvt. Ltd (Environmental Design Solutions)
Training, Passive Solar Design, Daylight & Simulations for Green
Buildings · (2014 - 2014)

V.K.Krishna Menon college of Science Hsc., Science · (2009 - 2011)

St. Mary's Convent High School SSC · (2003 - 2008)